Guide to the Edwin and Terry Murray Comic Book Collection
Edwin and Terry Murray Comic Book Collection
Murray, Edwin, and Terry Murray (collectors)
298 Linear Feet 67,600 Items
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University
Edwin L. and Terry A. Murray, brothers residing in Durham, N.C., have been collectors of comic books and other "pulp culture" for forty years. Terry is the author of "Science Fiction Magazine Story Index, 1926-1995" (McFarland, 1999).
The collection is notable for its comprehensive holdings of DC and Marvel comics from the mid-1960s to 2001. Most major American sub-genres are represented, and there are several hundred alternative comics from the late 1960s and early 1970s. About one-third of the issues date from before 1970. Publishers represented in the collection include: Aardvark-Vanaheim, Ace, ACG, Adventure, All-Star, Apple, Archie, Atlas, Boy, Buster Brown, Charlton, Classics Illustrated, Comico, Dark Horse, DC, Dell, Disney, Eagle, EC, Eclipse, Epic, Eternity, First, Fleetway, Giant, Gladstone, Gold Key, Harvey, Hero, Image, Impact, Kitchen Sink, Lev Gleason, Malibu, Manga, Marvel, Pioneer, QC, Topps, Valiant, Vista, Warp, Whitman and Wild Storm. DC titles represented in the collection include: Action Comics, Adventure Comics, Detective Comics, Batman, Superman, Flash, Green Lantern, Wonder Woman, Superboy, Supergirl and Sgt. Rock. Marvel titles represented in the collection include: Avengers, Captain America, Captain Marvel, Fantastic Four, Daredevil, Incredible Hulk, Punisher, Spider-Man, Thor, and X-Men. Accessions (2010-0071) and (2010-0107) include additional comics that have not been interfiled into the collection.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. There may be a 48-hour delay in obtaining these materials.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Edwin and Terry Murray Comic Book Collection was received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2002 and 2010.
Biographical Note
Edwin L. and Terry A. Murray, brothers residing in Durham, N.C., have been collectors of comic books and other "pulp culture" for forty years. Edwin published his own fanzines, Vertigo! and Trefoil, from the late 1960s through the mid 1980s. He graduated from Duke University in 1972. Edwin was at the center of comics fandom in the 1960s and 1970s. Terry, a science fiction expert, is the author of Science Fiction Magazine Story Index, 1926-1995 (McFarland, 1999).
Collection Overview
The Murray comic collection is notable for its size, depth, and comprehensive holdings of Marvel and DC comics from the mid-1960s to 2001. Most major American genres are represented, including superhero, crime, sci-fi, western, romance, funny animal, biography, humor, war, and horror. Some promotional comics are included, along with a selection of underground comics from the late 1960s through the 1980s. The earliest issues in the collection date from the late 1930s, and about one-third of the issues dates from before 1970. In addition to Marvel and DC, other publishers substantially represented in the collection include: Atlas, Charlton, Dark Horse, Dell, Disney, Eclipse, First, Gladstone, Gold Key, Image, Malibu, Quality, Valiant, and WaRP Graphics. The comic books are a separately cataloged and housed subcollection of the Edwin and Terry Murray Collection of Pulp Culture.
The collection has been organized into five series. The first three series of regular-format comics are arranged by publisher: DC,Marvel, and Assorted Small Publishers. Within the DC and Marvel series, issues are alphabetized by indicia title within each box. The indicia, or small print usually found at the bottom of the first page or the inside front cover, are the publisher's official identifying information. The Assorted Small Publishers series is organized by publisher, then indicia title. The Underground comics, including various size formats, have been organized separately (by publisher, then indicia title) into a fourth series. The fifth series contains Oversize or large-format comics, arranged by publisher, then indicia title. Cover titles are listed only when they differ from the indicia title, or when there are multiple cover titles under one indicia title housed in the same box. Box numbers are not always sequential; some numbers in the sequence have been skipped. Two supplementary container lists provide greater intellectual access by rearranging the numbered boxes into lists by title (arranged alphabetically) and decade of publication.
The DC series, dating from the 1930s to 2002, contains near-complete runs of Action Comics, Adventure Comics,Detective Comics, Batman, Superman, Flash, Green Lantern,Wonder Woman, Superboy, Supergirl, and Sgt. Rock. The collection also includes a large number of war comics, western comics, science fiction comics, horror comics, and some romance comics. Modern writers such as Alan Moore, Frank Miller, and Neil Gaiman are also heavily represented. Nearly every DC comic published from the 1970s onward is part of the collection, including the bulk of comics that appeared under the Vertigo imprint.
The Marvel series, dating from the 1940s to 2002, contains near-complete runs of Avengers,Captain America, Fantastic Four, Daredevil, Incredible Hulk, Punisher, Spider-Man, Thor, and X-Men. Some Captain Marvel titles are included in this series; other Captain Marvel issues and early Marvel titles (under Atlas publications) can be found in the Assorted Small Publishers series. First issues include Amazing Fantasy Introducing Spider-Man and Incredible Hulk. Early titles in the Marvel series include the western comics Kid Colt Outlaw and Two-Gun Kid. Science fiction, war comics, and horror comics are also part of the series. Other titles of note include Black Panther, one of the first black superheroes, and Northstar, the first mainstream openly gay superhero. The work of writer/editor Stan Lee and artist Jack Kirby, considered by many to have transformed the comics industry in the 1960s and 1970s, is well represented here. Other writers and artists include Todd McFarlane, Rob Liefeld, and Jim Lee, who eventually left Marvel to form Image (Image publications are included in the Assorted Small Publishers series).
The Assorted Small Publishers series, dating from the 1930s to the early 2000s, represents nearly one-hundred seventy publishers. Significant or substantial holdings include works published by Adventure; Archie; Atlas; Charlton; Comico; Dark Horse; Dell; Disney; Eclipse; Epic, an imprint of Marvel; Fawcett; First; Gilberton; Gladstone; Gold Key; Image; Kitchen Sink; Lev Gleason; Malibu; promotional comics by Buster Brown and Will Eisner; Quality; Timely; Topps; WaRP; and Valiant. The earliest published titles in this series, all from the 1930s, are Dell's Dick Tracy, Moon Mullins,Terry and the Pirates, and Wash Tubbs. Other notable early publications dating from the 1940s are Amazing Comics, Archie Comics, Captain Marvel,Classics Illustrated, Comics on Parade, Crime Does Not Pay, Daredevil, Human Torch, Lone Ranger, Marge's Little Lulu, Plastic Man,Red Dragon Comics, Sub-Mariner Comics, and Walt Disney and Warner Bros. adaptations.
The Underground Comics series dates from the 1960s to the 1980s, with the bulk published during the 1970s. Publishers substantially represented include Apex Novelties, Krupps Comic Works (publisher of Kitchen Sink Enterprises), Last Gasp, Rip Off Press, and Print Mint. The representative sampling of comics in this series is considered "underground" because of their unconventional storylines and explicit content. Published largely in San Francisco, underground comics frequently satirized "hippie" life in the '70s. This series includes the titles Death Rattle, Despair, Fabulous Furry Freak Brothers, Jesus Comics, Mr. Natural, R. Crumb's Comics and Stories, Slow Death, Skull, and Zap Comix. The work of prominent artists/writers R. Crumb, Gilbert Shelton, and Frank Stack (aka Foolbert Sturgeon) is heavily represented. Also included is Snarf (no. 3) with cover by guest illustrator, Will Eisner.
The fifth series comprises Oversize or large-format comics and graphic novels from a variety of publishers, housed separately due to their size. Publishers include DC, Marvel, Dark Horse, Epic, Gladstone, and WaRP Graphics.
This collection also includes unprocessed additions, Acc. 2010-0071 and 2010-0107. Boxlists for these comics have been added to the end of this finding aid.
Subject Headings
These are searchable subject entries for this collection. Performing a search on these subjects in the Duke University Libraries online catalog will bring up other related research materials.
Murray, Edwin L.
Murray, Terry A., 1953-
Batman (Comic strip).
Fantastic four (Comic strip).
Flash Gordon (Comic strip).
Green Lantern (Comic strip).
Spider-Man (Comic strip).
Hulk (Comic strip).
Superman (Comic strip).
Wonder Woman (Comic strip).
X-Men (Comic strip).
Captain America (Comic strip).
Avengers (Comic strip).
Captain Marvel (Comic strip).
Dick Tracy (Comic strip).
Flash (Fictitious character).
Daredevil (Fictitious character).
Andrews, Archie (Fictitious character).
Comic books, strips, etc
Advertising -- Comic books, strips, etc
Biography -- Comic books, strips, etc
Romance comic books, strips, etc
Horror comic books, strips, etc
Animals -- Comic books, strips, etc
Detective and mystery comic books, strips, etc
Underground comic books, strips, etc
Science fiction comic books, strips, etc
Teenagers -- Comic books, strips, etc
War -- Comic books, strips, etc
Superhero comic books, strips, etc
Erotic comic books, strips, etc
Fantasy comic books, strips, etc
Graphic novels
Western comic books, strips, etc
Hippies -- Comic books, strips, etc
African Americans -- Comic books, strips, etc
Gays -- Comic books, strips, etc
Murray, Edwin L.
Murray, Terry A., 1953-.
McFarlane, Todd
Moore, Alan, 1953-.
Liefeld, Rob
Kirby, Jack
Lee, Jim
Crumb, R.
Shelton, Gilbert
Stack, Frank
Sturgeon, Foolbert
Miller, Frank, 1957-.
Gaiman, Neil
Lee, Stan
Eisner, Will
DC Comics, Inc
Marvel Comics Group
Dark Horse Comics
Archie Comics Group
Charlton Comics
Eclipse Comics
First Comics, Inc
Image Comics
Malibu Comics
Quality Comics Group
Valiant (Firm).
WaRP Graphics
Contents of Collection
- DC Comics
  - Contents of Box 1: (Box 1)
    - Title from indicia: Adventure Comics, Issues from: 1970s,1980s
      - Cover Title: Adventure Comics, Issues from: 1980s
      - Cover Title: Aquaman, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Black Orchid, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Dial H for Hero, Issues from: 1980s
      - Cover Title: The Spectre, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Superboy, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Supergirl, Issues from: 1970s
  - Contents of Box 2: (Box 2)
    - Title from indicia: Adventure Comics, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Supergirl
    - Title from indicia: Aquaman, Issues from: 1960s,1970s
    - Title from indicia: The Phantom Stranger, Issues from: 1960s,1970s
    - Title from indicia: Supergirl, Issues from: 1970s
  - Contents of Box 3: (Box 3)
    - Title from indicia: All-Star Western, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: All-Star Western, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Pow Wow Smith, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Outlaw, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Batman, Issues from: 1960s
      Issues 145-146, 148-152, 155-169, 181, 183-184, 186, 188-189
    - Title from indicia: Rima, the Jungle Girl, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Sugar and Spike, Issues from: 1950s,1960s,1970s
    - Title from indicia: Weird Mystery Tales, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Weird Western Tales, Issues from: 1970s,1980s
      - Cover Title: Weird Western Tales, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Jonah Hex, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Scalphunter, Issues from: 1970s,1980s
  - Contents of Box 4: (Box 4)
    - Title from indicia: Detective Comics, Issues from: 1949-1956
      Issues 144-147, 149-155, 157-180, 182-192, 194-224, 226-234
  - Contents of Box 5: (Box 5)
    - Title from indicia: Detective Comics, Issues from: 1956-1966
      Issues 235-351
  - Contents of Box 6: (Box 6)
    - Title from indicia: Detective Comics, Issues from: 1939 -1948
      Issues 23, 31-32, 37, 39, 41-42, 46, 49, 52, 58, 59, 61, 64-72, 74, 76-77, 79-81, 83-84, 86-87, 89, 91-93, 95-96, 98-101, 103-112, 115-117, 119-122, 124-125, 127-130, 134-135, 139-141
  - Contents of Box 7: (Box 7)
    - Title from indicia: Mystery in Space, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Strange Adventures, Issues from: 1960s
  - Contents of Box 8: (Box 8)
    - Title from indicia: Strange Adventures, Issues from: 1950s,1960s
  - Contents of Box 9: (Box 9)
    - Title from indicia: Batman, Issues from: 1960s
      Issues 147, 153-154, 176
      - Cover Title: 80 pg. Giant Batman
    - Title from indicia: Batman Annual, Issues from: 1960s
      - Cover Title: Giant Batman Annual
    - Title from indicia: The Flash, Issues from: 1960s
      - Cover Title: Giant Flash
    - Title from indicia: Flash Annual, Issues from: 1960s
      - Cover Title: Giant Flash Annual
    - Title from indicia: 80 pg. Giant Magazine, Issues from: 1960s
      - Cover Title: 80 pg. Giant Batman, Issues from: 1960s
      - Cover Title: 80 pg. Giant The Flash, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Justice League of America, Issues from: 1960s
      - Cover Title: 80 pg. Giant Justice League of America
    - Title from indicia: Secret Origins, Issues from: 1960s
      - Cover Title: DC presents Secret Origins
    - Title from indicia: Strange Adventures, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Superman, Issues from: 1960s
      - Cover Title: 80 pg. Giant Superman
    - Title from indicia: Superman Annual, Issues from: 1960s
      - Cover Title: Giant Superman Annual
    - Title from indicia: World's Finest Comics, Issues from: 1960s
      - Cover Title: Giant World's Finest presents Batman and Superman
  - Contents of Box 10: (Box 10)
    - Title from indicia: Superboy, Issues from: 1950s,1960s
    - Title from indicia: Superman, Issues from: 1940s,1960s
  - Contents of Box 11: (Box 11)
    - Title from indicia: The Adventures of Alan Ladd, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Dale Evans Comics, Issues from: 1940s,1950s
    - Title from indicia: Hopalong Cassidy, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Jimmy Wakely, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Legion of Super-Heroes, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Real Facts Comics, Issues from: 1940s
    - Title from indicia: Secret Six, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Sergeant Bilko, Issues from: 1950s
      - Cover Title: Sgt. Bilko
    - Title from indicia: The Spectre, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Superboy, Issues from: 1940s,1950s
  - Contents of Box 12: (Box 12)
    - Title from indicia: Action Comics, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Action Comics (Superman)
    - Title from indicia: Dynamic Classics, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Dynamic Classics starring Batman
    - Title from indicia: Ghosts, Issues from: 1970s,1980s
    - Title from indicia: Mystery in Space, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Superboy, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Superboy, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Superboy starring the Legion of Superheroes, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Super-Heroes Battle Super-Gorillas, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Welcome Back, Kotter, Issues from: 1970s
  - Contents of Box 13: (Box 13)
    - Title from indicia: Detective Comics, Issues from: 1966-1977
      Issues 352-468
  - Contents of Box 14: (Box 14)
    - Title from indicia: Detective Comics, Issues from: 1977-1989
      Issues 469-553, 558-600
  - Contents of Box 15: (Box 15)
    - Title from indicia: Falling in Love, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Legion of Super-Heroes, Issues from: 1980s
      - Cover Title: Legion of Superheroes
    - Title from indicia: The Legion of Super-Heroes, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Original Swamp Thing Saga, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Prez, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Prez: First Teen President
    - Title from indicia: Secret Hearts, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Superboy, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Superboy starring The Legion of Super-Heroes
    - Title from indicia: Superboy & The Legion of Super-Heroes, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Superboy & The Legion of Superheroes
    - Title from indicia: Young Love, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Young Romance, Issues from: 1970s
  - Contents of Box 16: (Box 16)
    - Title from indicia: Batman, Issues from: 1970s,1980s
      Issues 219-222, 224-227, 229-232, 234-237, 239-344
  - Contents of Box 17: (Box 17)
    - Title from indicia: Batman, Issues from: 1940s,1950s,1960s,1980s
      Issues 53-91, 170-175, 177-180, 190-192, 194-197, 199-202, 204-207, 209-212, 214-217, 345-374
  - Contents of Box 18: (Box 18)
    - Title from indicia: Action Comics, Issues from: 1960s
      - Cover Title: Action Comics (Superman)
    - Title from indicia: Batman, Issues from: 1940s
      Issues 17-46, 48-52
  - Contents of Box 19: (Box 19)
    - Title from indicia: Action Comics, Issues from: 1960s
      - Cover Title: Action Comics (Superman), Issues from: 1960s
      - Cover Title: 80 pg. Giant Action Comics presents Supergirl, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: 80 pg. Giant, Issues from: 1960s
      - Cover Title: 80 pg. Giant Batman, Issues from: 1960s
      - Cover Title: 80 pg. Giant Jimmy Olsen, Issues from: 1960s
      - Cover Title: 80 pg. Giant Lois Lane, Issues from: 1960s
      - Cover Title: 80 pg. Giant Secret Origins, Issues from: 1960s
      - Cover Title: 80 pg. Giant Sgt. Rock's Prize Battle Tales, Issues from: 1960s
      - Cover Title: 80 pg. Giant Superboy, Issues from: 1960s
      - Cover Title: 80 pg. Giant Superman, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Sea Devils, Issues from: 1960s
  - Contents of Box 20: (Box 20)
    - Title from indicia: Adventure Comics, Issues from: 1960s
      - Cover Title: Adventure Comics featuring Superboy & The Legion of Super-Heroes, Issues from: 1960s
      - Cover Title: Supergirl starring in Adventure Comics, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Batman, Issues from: 1960s
      Issues 182, 185, 187, 193, 198, 203, 208, 213
    - Title from indicia: Lois Lane Annual, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Our Army at War, Issues from: 1960s
      - Cover Title: Sgt. Rock's Prize Battle Tales, Issues from: 1960s
      - Cover Title: Sgt. Rock's 6 Battle Tales, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Sgt. Rock's Prize Battle Stories, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Superboy, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Superboy Annual, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Superman, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Superman's Girl Friend Lois Lane, Issues from: 1960s
      - Cover Title: Lois Lane
    - Title from indicia: Superman's Pal Jimmy Olsen, Issues from: 1960s
      - Cover Title: Jimmy Olsen
  - Contents of Box 21: (Box 21)
    - Title from indicia: Adventure Comics, Issues from: 1950s,1960s
      - Cover Title: Adventure Comics (Superboy), Issues from: 1950s,1960s
      - Cover Title: Adventure Comics featuring Superboy & The Legion of Superheroes, Issues from: 1950s,1960s
  - Contents of Box 22: (Box 22)
    - Title from indicia: Adventure Comics, Issues from: 1940s,1950s
      - Cover Title: Adventure Comics (Superboy)
    - Title from indicia: Claw the Unconquered, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Korak, Son of Tarzan, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Ragman, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Starfire, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Super DC Giant, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Challenges of the Unknown, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Love 1971, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Strange Flying Saucer Adventures, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Top Guns of the West, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: The Tarzan Family, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Weird Worlds, Issues from: 1970s
  - Contents of Box 23: (Box 23)
    - Title from indicia: Action Comics, Issues from: 1980s
      - Cover Title: Action Comics (Superman)
    - Title from indicia: Firestorm, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: The Fury of Firestorm, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Fury of Firestorm Annual, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Warlord, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Warlord Annual, Issues from: 1980s
  - Contents of Box 24: (Box 24)
    - Title from indicia: Action Comics, Issues from: 1970s,1980s
      - Cover Title: Action Comics (Superman)
  - Contents of Box 25: (Box 25)
    - Title from indicia: Action Comics, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: DC 100-Page Super Spectacular, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: The Flash, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Justice League of America. Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Love Stories, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Tarzan, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: World's Greatest Superheroes, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: DC Super Stars, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: The Flash, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Giant The Flash
    - Title from indicia: Ghosts, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Ghosts Special, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Justice League of America, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Giant Justice League
    - Title from indicia: Super-Star Holiday Special, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Superstar Holiday Special
    - Title from indicia: Super-Team Family, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: World's Finest Comics, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Giant World's Finest Comics
  - Contents of Box 26: (Box 26)
    - Title from indicia: Dark Mansion of Forbidden Love, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Forbidden Tales of Dark Mansion, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Ghost Castle, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Plop!, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Strange Adventures, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Weird Mystery Tales, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Wonder Woman Spectacular, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Wonder Woman, Issues from: 1980s
  - Contents of Box 27: (Box 27)
    - Title from indicia: Superman, Issues from: 1960s,1970s
    - Title from indicia: Wonder Woman, Issues from: 1970s,1980s
  - Contents of Box 28: (Box 28)
    - Title from indicia: Superman, Issues from: 1970s,1980s
  - Contents of Box 29: (Box 29)
    - Title from indicia: Super DC Giant, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: The Best of the Brave and the Bold featuring Batman, Flash, and Metamorpho, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Love 1970, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Top Guns of the West, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Western Comics, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Superman, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: World's Finest Comics, Issues from: 1970s,1980s
  - Contents of Box 30: (Box 30)
    - Title from indicia: Superman, Issues from: 1950s,1960s
    - Title from indicia: World's Finest Comics, Issues from: 1970s